Guide to the E. Ethelbert Miller papers, 1936-2021, bulk 1962-2018 MS2215
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
E. Ethelbert Miller papers
1962-2018
1936-2021
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
MS2215
138.5 Linear Feet
Included are correspondence, fliers, posters, journals, photographs, interviews, and articles related to the artistic life of poet E. Ethelbert Miller dating from 1936-2021 with the bulk from 1962-2018. The collection also contains poet files with correspondence, fliers, programs, posters, photographs, interviews, and articles relating to specific poets within the Washington, D.C. area. A small portion of the collection (Series 2) relates to the work of D.C. Poet Laureate Dolores Kendrick.
Biographical Note
E. Ethelbert Miller is a writer and literary activist. He is the board chair of the Institute for Policy Studies (IPS), a progressive think tank located in Washington, D.C. For ten years he has been the editor of Poet Lore, the oldest poetry magazine published in the United States. In 1996, he delivered the commencement address at Emory and Henry College and was awarded an honorary degree of Doctor of Literature. Mr. Miller has been a Fulbright Senior Specialist Program Fellow to Israel in 2004 and 2012. In February 2006 he was the keynote speaker at the 50th Anniversary of the Fulbright Program in Israel, at the Embassy of Israel in Washington, D.C.
Miller is the founder and former chair of the Humanities Council of Washington, D.C. He served as a Commissioner for the D.C. Commission on the Arts and Humanities from 1997-2008. He is board emeritus for the PEN/ Faulkner Foundation.
The author of several collections of poetry, he has written memoirs including Fathering Words: The Making of An African American Writer (2000) and The 5th Inning (2009). Fathering Words was selected by the D.C. Public Library for its DC WE READ, one book, one city program in 2003. His poetry anthology In Search of Color Everywhere was awarded the PEN Oakland Josephine Miles Award in 1994.
In 1978 "E. Ethelbert Miller Day" was proclaimed in D.C. on September 28, 1978. Miller would receive the Mayor's Arts Award in 1982 for Literature, the Public Humanities Award in 1988, the Columbia Merit Award in 1994, and made an honorary citizen of Baltimore on July 17, 1994.
On May 21, 2001 " E. Ethelbert Miller Day" was proclaimed in Jackson, Tennessee. In 2001 and 2003 he was honored at the National Book Festival hosted by Laura Bush. In February 2007 he was awarded the Barnes & Noble Writers for Writers Award by Poets and Writers. In May 2007, Miller was awarded a Virginia Center for Creative Arts Fellowship. In June 2009 a Sea Change Fellowship by the Gaea Foundation.
Mr. Miller has taught at University of Nevada, Las Vegas, American University, George Mason University, and Emory and Henry College. For a number of years he was a core faculty member with the Bennington Writing Seminars. He delivered the Seminars commencement address in 1999, 2003 and 2013.
From 1974-2000 he was the founder and director of the Ascension Poetry Reading Series which presented hundreds of African American poets and poets of color to the general public. In 1997 he worked with the Inter-Governmental Philatelic Corporation (IGPC) and was responsible for placing twelve African American writers on postage stamps issued by Ghana and Uganda. The writers honored were Maya Angelou, Rita Dove, Mari Evans, Henry Louis Gates, Jr, Charles Johnson, June Jordan, Toni Cade Bambara, Sterling A. Brown, Alex Haley, Stephen Henderson, Zora Neale Hurston and Richard Wright.
In 2003 Miller's poems were selected for sculpture installations at the Petworth and DuPont Circle Metro stations. Mr. Miller is often heard on National Public Radio. He is host and producer of The Scholars on UDC-TV and writes a regular monthly column, E on DC for Capital Community News. His E-Notes has been a popular blog since 2004. On April 19, 2015, Mr. Miller was inducted into the Washington DC Hall of Fame.
Scope and Contents
A meticulous record keeper, Ethelbert Miller has amassed correspondence, fliers, posters, journals, photographs, interviews, and articles pertaining to his career ranging from 1936-2021 with the bulk covering 1962-2018. His journals, revised works and collaborative correspondence allow the opportunity to study his evolving writing process. Through the many features, articles, interviews, reviews, awards and certificates, we are able to understand how enthusiastically Miller has been received by his peers within the poetry community as well as outside it.
The collection also contains the subseries "Poet Files," which contains correspondence, promotional materials and works by various poets within the Washington, D.C. area that has been amassed by Ethelbert Miller.
A small portion of the collection (Series 2) relates to the work of D.C. Poet Laureate Dolores Kendrick.
Arrangement
Organized into 2 series: Ethelbert Miller materials and Dolores Kendrick materials. Series 1 is further organized into 11 subseries.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. Boxes 213 and 214 in Series 1 Subseries 6 have been restricted for 50 years (until 2072) because they contain copies of manuscripts and other writings sent to Miller by other authors, some of which may have not given permission for their works to be accessed.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of E. Ethelbert Miller, 2007 January 29 (2007.029), May 2017 (2017.025), January 2018 (2018.002) There have been many subsequent donations. Please ask for assistance if you would like more information about these additions.
Separated Materials
Four books were removed from the ACC2017.025 donation and added to the Special Collections stacks. These include Hoodoo 3, Hoodoo 4, Brown Sugar 3, and In Daddy's Arms I am Tall.
Two poetry chapbooks by Essex Hemphill from ACC2021.020 and two additional books--Guns in the Hands of Artists and A Parallel Road--from ACC2021.035 were cataloged separetely in 2021-2022.
Related Materials
Due to Miller's connection to other DC-area poets and literary groups, there may be related materials in other collections within the Special Collections Research Center. Some collections to consult include: MS2007 Grace Cavalieri papers; MS2320 Daniel Schwarz DC poetry oral history collection; and MS2389 Beltway Poetry Quarterly records. Miller's 2021 donation (2021.035) included five editions of Black Box, a recorded poetry magazine. These tapes compliment the SCRC's exisiting collection, MS2172. Miller has a podcast titled "on the margin" From the online description: "On The Margin is a radio program that examines our literary culture. The program serves as a public forum for published writers and scholars. The show is for people who are book lovers. On The Margin also places an emphasis on providing a platform for people engaged in running literary institutions such as libraries, bookstores and creative writing programs. On The Margin aims to explore the link between culture and politics, offering the community a better understanding of the motion of history."
This podcast is part of the WPFW archives. http://www.wpfwfm.org/radio/programming/archived-shows
Poets, American; Poetry -- African American poets; Photographs; Poetry -- Workshops; Performance poetry; Washington (D.C.); Walker, Alice; Cavalieri, Grace; Kendrick, Dolores; Miller, E. Ethelbert; Alvarez, Julia
- Ethelbert Miller materials, 1962-2018; 1940-2021; Series 1; Miller, E. Ethelbert
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains promotional material, correspondence, poet files, works in progress, publications and other material that chronicles the career of E. Ethelbert Miller. The materials date from 1940 to 2021, with the bulk of the material dating from 1962-2018.
  Arrangement
  Arranged into 11 subseries: All material donated before 2008, Poet files, Publications, Works in progress, Projects, programs and publicity, Correspondence, Oversize materials, Posters, Personal materials, Organizations, and Audiovisual materials
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 213 and 214 in Series 1 Subseries 6 have been restricted for 50 years (until 2072) because they contain copies of manuscripts and other writings sent to Miller by other authors, some of which may have not given permission for their works to be accessed.
  Poetry -- African American poets; Correspondence; Public speaking; Cavalieri, Grace; Alvarez, Julia
  - All material donated before 2008, Series 1 Subseries 1; 24 linear feet
    General
    This subseries consists of material donated by E. Ethelbert Miller in 2007. It contains correspondence, articles by or about the author, promotional material, poetry in progress and completed, journals, certificates and awards and other material related to the life and work of E. Ethelbert Miller. Please note that correspondence contained within this subseries may overlap with the Poet files within subseries 2.
    Original order has been maintained
    - Biography, bibliography (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - College papers (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - College papers (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - College papers, projects, proposals (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Early work: Poet Gone Nova (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Early work: Poems Created to Conform to Celestial Circles (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Early work: poems (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Early work: poems (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Early work: poems (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Early work: poems (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Early work: poems (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Early work: poems (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Early work: poems (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Early work: poems (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Early work: poems (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Early work: Wanderlust (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Early work: The Land of Smiles and the Land of No Smiles (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Poetry: Before the Flood (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Poetry: Andromeda (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Poetry: Seasons of Hunger/Cry of Rain (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Poems: Poet Gone Nova (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Poetry: Selected poems (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Poetry: Selected poems (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Poetry: Sketches (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Poetry: Poems to Conform to Celestial Circles (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Poetry: Women Surviving Massacres and Men (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Poetry: Panama (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Poetry: Panama (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Poems (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Poetry: Memory Like Arrows Falling from the Sky (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Poetry: Where are the Love Poems for Dictators, edited version (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Poetry: Where are the Love Poems for Dictators, edited version (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Poetry: Where are the Love Poems for Dictators, edited version (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Poetry: Where are the Love Poems for Dictators, edited version (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Poetry: First Line, new and selected poems (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Poetry: First Light, new and selected poems (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Poetry: First Light, new and selected poems (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Poetry: Nicaragua (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Speeches (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Works by friends (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Opera: Heavens Where Lovers Go (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Anthology: Beyond the Frontier materials (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Anthology: Beyond the Frontier materials (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Novel: The House of Spiders, draft (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The Novel as a Geometry of Design (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Drafts of work (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Fiction, drafts (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Buddha Weeping in Winter, materials (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Novel: untitled draft (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Fathering Words: proposal correspondence (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Fathering Words: edits (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Fathering words: edits (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Fathering words (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Poems (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Poems: drafts (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Poems (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Poems (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Poems (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Poems (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Love Letters for Literacy materials (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Common and Political Crimes: the Absence of Love (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - The Black Writer: from Communism to Culture, 12/1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous edited works (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous edited works (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Publications list (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Publications: New Directions, 07/1977 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Publications: Oo-sh'bop, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Publications: The Howard Poets in Perspective, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Publications: New Directions, 10/1978 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Publications: Dawn Magazine, 07/1980 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Publications: Sagala, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Publications: Omowe, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Publications: New Directions, 07/1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Publications: Sol, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Publications: Washington review, 04/1984 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Publications: the Washington Review, 07/1984 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Publications: Working Cultures, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Publications: the Capstone, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Publications: Washington Review, 03/1985 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Publications: the Capstone, 08/26/1985 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Publications: the Party's Over, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Publications: World's World, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Publications: Footwork '85, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Publications: Washington Review, 01/1986 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Publications: Working Cultures, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Publications: the Capstone, 02/09/1984 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Publications: Reflections, 06/1987 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Publications: the City Paper, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Publications: World's Word, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Publications: New Directions, 10/1988 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Publications: Footwork '88, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Publications: Nile Valley Papyrus, 05/1989 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Publications: Catalyst, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Publications: Erehwon, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Publications: New Directions, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Publications: the People of the District of Columbia, 02/08/1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Publications: Tailwind, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Publications: Zora, 01/1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Publications: the Nation, 05/23/1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Publications: Poets and Writers, 06/1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Publications: Poets and Writers, 06/1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Publications: Nacada, 10/12/1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Publications: the Drumming, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Publications: Black Issues in Higher Education, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Publications: Seeking the Beauty of Suns, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Publications: the New Press, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Publications: Oil on the Waters, the Black Diaspora, 04/20/1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Publications: Black Poets Should Live, 04/23/1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Publications: Poets and Writers, 10/1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Publications: Poets and Writers, 10/1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Publications: Listen to Our Diverse Voices, 12/1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Publications: Poetry and Literature, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Publications: Come Sunday, 03/07/1999 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Publications: Center in the City, 05/1999 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Publications: Capstone, 06/28/1999 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Publications: Center in the City, 10/1999 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Publications: American Visions, 07/1999 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Publications: Politics and Prose, 10/1999 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Publications: Black Issues in Higher Education, 11/25/1999 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Publications: the Capstone, 03/29/1999 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Publications: AWP Reading Series, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Publications: Writer's Bloc, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Publications: the Washington Review, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Publications: Art and Soul, 02/27/2000 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Publications: Art and Soul, 02/2001 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Publications: Publishers Weekly, 05/08/2000 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Publications: Washington Flyer, 10/2000 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Publications: the Writer's Chronicle, 12/2000 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Publications: St. Martins Press, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Publications: Emory and Henry, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Publications: Sojourners Magazine, 12/2001 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Publications: Ace Dialogue, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Publications: Northwestern University Journal, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Publications: Bsidian III, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Publications: Four Corners, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Publications: Word Works Books (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Publications: By Words (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Publicatoins: Washington Writers Publishing House, series XX (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Publications: Scholarships, Grants, Loans, and Financial Aid infromation for Military Students (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Publications: Hoo Doo (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Publications: The Distance Traveled...a History (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Publications: Working Cultures (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Publications: Working Cultures (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Publications: Transitions (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Contracts (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Articles (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper articles (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Articles, interviews (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Articles (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Articles (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Articles (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Articles (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Articles (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Articles (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper articles (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Articles (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Articles, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Articles, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Articles, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Articles, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Articles, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Articles, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Articles, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Articles, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Articles, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Articles, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Articles, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Articles, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Articles, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Articles, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Articles, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Articles, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Articles (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Articles, clippings (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Articles, clippings (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Articles, clippings (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Articles, features (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Articles, interviews (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Interview: New Directions, 04/1986 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Interview: Washington Post profile, 07/06/2000 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Interview: Folio, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Interviews (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Interviews (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Interviews (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Interviews (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Features: Black Issues in Higher Education, 12/25/1994 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Feature: Oak Leaves, 02/14/1996 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Feature: Arlington Virginian, 05/08/1996 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Feature: Magazine for the Arts, 05/1996 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Feature: Washingtonian, 04/2000 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Features, reviews (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Profiles, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Profiles, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Profiles, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Profiles, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Profiles, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Profiles, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Profiles, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Book review: Legacy, 10/1996 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Review: Black Issues in Higher Education, 11/13/1997 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Review: Black Issues, 08/2000 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Review: QBR, 10/2000 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Reviews (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Reviews (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Book reviews (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Press releases (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Periodicals: Third World (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Periodicals: Third World (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Periodicals: Poetry Now (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Periodicals: The People (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Periodicals: miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Periodicals magazines (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Periodicals: miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Periodicals: miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Periodicals journals (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Periodicals: miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Periodicals: miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Periodicals: miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Periodicals magazines (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Magazines: Insight, 05/1986 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Magazines: Humanities, 03/1996 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Magazines: Poets and Writers, 10/1977 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Magazines: Civilization, 1/1977 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Magazines: Civilization, 11/1997 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Capstone (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Magazines journals: miscellanous (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Magazines, journals: miscellanous (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Programs, flyers, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Programs, flyers, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Programs, flyers, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Programs, flyers, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Programs, flyers, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Programs, flyers, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Programs, flyers, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Programs, flyers, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Programs, flyers, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Programs, flyers, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Programs, flyers, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Programs, flyers, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Programs, flyers, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Programs, flyers, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Programs, flyers, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Programs, flyers, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Programs, flyers, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Programs, flyers, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Programs, flyers, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Programs, flyers, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Programs, announcements, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Programs, announcements, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Programs, announcements, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Program: PMLA, 11/2000 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Programs, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Programs (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Programs (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Programs (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Programs (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Programs, flyers (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Programs, flyers (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Programs, flyers (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Programs, flyers (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Programs, flyers (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Programs, flyers (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Programs, flyers (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Programs, flyers, invitations (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Programs, flyers, invitations (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Flyers, posters (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Programs, flyers (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Posters (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Flyers (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Invitations to Isreal fulbright program (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Invitations to Isreal fulbright program (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Programs, flyers, posters (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Programs (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Programs (Box 7, Folder 3)